Oh no bro.
Look here guy
Peti or Chevette no place.
It can't be enough.
I'm going to start selling candy again on the street.
I can't wait for things to happen again in my life.
It's on there in the center now,
investing I don't know,
in peaceful water,
starting to make some money because otherwise we'll keep waiting for things to
fall from the sky and then we'll reach the limit of stupidity.
He knows
find something cheap like R$1 from Novo?
You know,
but there's no Cara here.
When I was here looking for candy,
she got a message for me saying that she wants me to go there
now and go for a walk with her dog.
Just see that I'm on foot.
You have to go to the address here.
I'll secure my dog Walker here and we'll go.
Thank God.
At 49 of the 2nd old time he had to be Corinthian.
Hand girl all right?
I knew I came to the supermarket nearby.
Can I have 1 bag?
Thanks.
And then people are fine.
She is Buma and he is Biorne.
Legal Biorne.
See you in a little while.
I already send a receipt.
I'm going for a walk.
I came to get an uncle dog and I'm taking two.
But the money is bigger too.
One hour of my day.
No no no no
guy 50 tale walking with dog uncle 1 hour old sky bro AI bro that old Massa.
I have a business idea and I need to run before the store closes old
Oh too low oh too low.